Ambition is a science fiction, history, mystery film directed by Tomek Bagiński.
A young apprentice struggles to master nanotechnology on an alien
world and prove herself to her enigmatic master.
Will her herculean goals remain tantalizingly out of reach, or will she
fulfill them and in the process, change life as we know it?
Master, played by Aidan Gillen.
Apprentice, played by Aisling Franciosi.
Naked Ambition 2, also known as 3D Naked Ambition (Chinese: 3D豪情), is a 2014 Hong Kong 3D sex
comedy film directed by Lee Kung-lok and starring Chapman To and Josie Ho.
It is a loose sequel to Chan Hing-ka and Dante Lam's 2003 film Naked Ambition.
Filming began in Tokyo in October 2013.
The film parodies the Japanese adult film industry through
various iconic scenes with exaggerated expressions.
The film explores themes of mind control, future,
apprentice, telekinesis, space.
The tone is thought_provoking and mind_bending.